family how are you well
familia qué tal estáis bueno
I'm definitely so if the
definitivamente estoy así que si en la
last time even that passed by here if it
última vez incluso que pasó por aquí si
's not the last it's the second to last and the
no es la última es la penúltima y el
last is the last video that we're going to have
último es el último vídeo que vamos a
here in this corner that as
tener aquí en este rincón que ya como
you can see is completely empty wait I'll
veis está completamente vacío espera me
move away a little so you can see it okay it's
alejó un poco para que lo veáis vale es
a corner where we have lived through
un es un rincón donde hemos vivido
many things where we have felt
muchísimas cosas donde hemos sentido
many things okay we have laughed we
muchísimas cosas vale nos hemos reído
have split our sides laughing
nos hemos partido de la risa algunas
sometimes even crying with laughter we
veces incluso llorando de la risa nos
see ourselves angry we have gotten pissed off we have
vemos enfadados nos hemos [__] hemos
used the floor we
utilizado metida el suelo
see ourselves we
nos vemos
have gotten very
nos hemos enfadado en mucho grado de
angry I have done everything here I have not done
rabia he hecho de todo aquí no he hecho
the interview Antonio David Flores done
la entrevista antonio david flores hecho
interviews Aurum Play we have done the
entrevistas aurum play hemos hecho el
squid game we have
juego del calamar hemos
done the report here when
hemos hecho de aquí el reportaje cuando
when La Sexta came when La
cuando vino la sexta cuando viene la
Sexta comes we were here the cameras of
sexta estuvimos aquí las cámaras de
Las Sexta around here the editors of La
lasexta por aquí los redactores de la
Sexta we have lived through many things here
sexta hemos vivido muchísimas cosas aquí
in this corner that today we
en este rincón del que ya hoy
definitely say goodbye to okay we
definitivamente nos despedimos vale nos
say goodbye to everything I already have the
despedimos todo ya tengo del estudio
new studio absolutely set up I don't know if I
nuevo absolutamente montado no sé si lo
will show it because I prefer  train it now
enseñaré porque prefiero entrenarlo ya
with its lights so you can see it well but I don't
con sus luces que lo veáis bien pero no
think there are any without lights or anything because I do
creo que hay sin luces ni nada porque
n't have electricity I don't have electricity or internet
no tengo luz no tengo luz ni internet
yet it's worth it the moment they
todavía vale en el momento que me dieron
gave me the keys to the house I
que nos dieron las llaves de la casa
ran as fast as I could I called
corrí toda la prisa posible
Endesa I presented all the
llamé a endesa le presenté toda la
documentation and everything so they would give me
documentación y todo para que me dieran
the registration as soon as possible I knew it would
el alta lo antes posible yo sabía que
take a few days but no way it
tardaría unos días pero ni de coña que
would be Thursday which is today
estaríamos a jueves que estamos hoy
and I still don't know anything else I don't know what to do
y todavía no sé nada más yo ya no sé qué
about presenting the offices I have done
hacer de presentar las oficinas he hecho
everything every day calling the
de todo todos los días llamándome a los
workers who are in summer I
trabajadores que están en verano me
imagine it will be in summer it seems that they are
imagino que será en verano se ve que son
like substitutes and they don't know anything or you
como suplentes y no saben nada o tú
call still tell us one thing and then I
llamas aún nos dice una cosa y luego los
use them corresponding land it's like they keep
utilizo terreno corresponde es como que
giving you the runaround without knowing and I
te van dando largas y sin saber y me
imagine it will be things in August no
imagino que serán cosas de agosto no por
therefore as long as I don't have any I can't
lo tanto mientras que no tenga alguno
have internet either because
puedo tener internet tampoco porque
until they activate the electricity
hasta que no me activen la luz que tiene
a technician has to come to put the
que venir un técnico a ponerte el
meter on you and register you okay because with
contador y darte el alta vale porque a
a new registration then the internet technician can't come either no so
una alta nueva pues no puede venir el
I sincerely  I promised to come back
que yo ya sinceramente os prometí volver
yesterday but I don't think so because I'm not counting on it
ayer pero no creo que sea que ya no
this week. I hope so, I hope that
cuento con que con que esta semana
suddenly today at
vuelva ojalá ojalá de repente hoy en
some point during the day the technician
algún momento del día venga el técnico
from Marchi will come, see the light or tomorrow and tomorrow
de marchi ve la luz o mañana y mañana
the internet technician will come too,
mismo también venga el técnico del
but less so, back with them
internet pero menos vuelto con ellos
seeing seeing the plan they are in
viendo viendo en el plan que están
because I don't count on them and well, it's
porque no cuento con ellos y bueno
already absolutely
necesita ya está absolutamente nos
set up for us, okay, it's absolutely set up
montaron vale es absolutamente montado
then at least he recorded something from there,
luego al menos grabó algo desde allí
okay, let it be a little bit
vale que sea un poquito
regarding
respecto al
the subject of the documentary, I've
respecto al tema del documental ya lo
seen almost the entire thing, I'm missing a little bit of
visto casi entero me falta un poquillo
them taking some notes because of
ellos tomando algunas notas porque por
course there is a video either on the
supuesto hay un vídeo bien en el canal
main channel or a live video on TV to the CEO,
principal o un directo en teles al ceo
but well, analyzing all the points, there
pero bien analizando todos los puntos no
are some things that seemed
hay algunas cosas que me han parecido un
absurd to me, honestly, there
despropósito sinceramente
are two scenes that I really didn't
son dos escenas que la verdad no me
expect at all and they seemed
esperaba para nada y me han parecido
embarrassing to me, I mean, even if it's
vergonzosas o sea aunque eso quede
recorded and even if I talk about it in
grabado y aunque lo hable en la
private, there are things that you don't put
intimidad hay cosas que tú no metes
inside when they are editing, okay, there is a
dentro cuando están editando vale hay un
moment in which Amador is showing off
momento en el que amador está enseñando
gadgets that are the work of a
artilugios que se trabajo de
survivor and he grabs how he grabs what
superviviente y coge como coge lo que
looks like an object
parece un objeto
and is going to say something  sharp object but it doesn't
y va a decir un objeto punzante pero no
seem to have the shape I don't know if you
parece haber tiene la forma no sé si me
understand me it has a vile shape and okay you
entiende tiene una forma vil y vale lo
pick it up like a stone that has a
coges como una piedra que tiene una
vile shape okay he picks it up and says down here
forma vil vale lo coge y le dice abajo
look this is what he likes now to
mira esto es lo que le gusta ahora en
open it
abrir
seems to me an
a mí me parece un comentario
unfortunate comment that you maybe in your
desafortunado que tú a lo mejor en tu
group is an older man we have seen in
grupo es un hombre mayor hemos visto en
amador who was very very majority who
amador que estaba muy muy mayoría que
makes that type of comments no but
hace ese tipo de comentarios no pero
some things that the man you make yourself
unas cosas que el hombre te hagás a
comment in private now a
comentar en la intimidad ya un hombre de
70 year old man you are not going to change his
70 años no lo vas a cambiar tú de
mentality and what is right and what is
mentalidad y de lo que está bien y lo
wrong and another thing is that you
que está mal y otra cosa es que tú
editing the video in the time in which we
editando el vídeo en la época en la que
live you put it okay this is what he
vivimos lo metas vale esto es lo que le
likes now well I think that there is a lot
gusta ahora bien yo creo que hay mucha
I think that there is a lot of criticism that
yo creo que hay muchas críticas que se
can be made of Javier right here we have
le pueden hacer por javier aquí mismo le
made a lot of criticism
hemos hecho un montones de críticas
now Xavier without needing to fall into
ahora xavier sin necesidad de caer en
that okay then there is another there is another part
eso vale luego hay otro hay otra parte
too that seems terrible to me it seems
también que me parece terrible me parece
unfortunate to me too and it is when amador
desafortunada también y es cuando amador
begins to tell an episode that he had
se pone a contar un episodio que tuvo
with the king with the king emeritus  today they
con el rey con el rey emérito a día de
were in a meeting they met
estuvieron en una reunión se encontraron
somewhere with him he didn't take a
en algún sitio con el no se hiciera unas
vacation and the king was staring at the
vacaciones y el rey se quedó mirando las
tits rice and dorados those
tetas arroz y dorados
are things there are a few
son cosas son hay unos cuantos de
episodes like that within the documentary and
episodios así dentro del documental y
then at the content level absolutely
luego a nivel de contenido absolutamente
nothing is worth it I understand that there are
nada vale yo entiendo que hay a las
people from that channel and people
personas de ese canal y a las personas
who are fans of amador and what
que son fan de amador y qué
without disrespecting really because
sin faltar al respeto de verdad porque
many of my audience are
muchas de mi audiencia son personas
older people too but there are people
mayores también pero hay personas a las
who can entertain me
que les pueden entretener a mí
sincerely from the heart I know
sinceramente de corazón sé maestro
boring teacher okay there is no rhythm there is no
aburrido vale no hay ritmo no hay
news okay look without going any further
novedades vale mirar sin ir más lejos
there are live shows on that channel on
hay directos en ese canal en el canal de
guamo's channel where amador tells more things
guamo donde amador cuenta más cosas
much more entertaining and much more
mucho más entretenida y mucho más
interesting okay it's not because he does it
interesante vale no es porque lo haga él
or because someone else would have done it I'm
o porque hubiera hecho otro estoy
saying what there is and that is that he doesn't tell
diciendo lo que hay y es que no cuenta
anything 50 something interesting instead of putting
nada 50 algo interesante en vez de poner
in the comment box envy and
en la caja de comentario envidias y
jealousy that's because you don't do it
celos eso es porque no lo haces tú
envious and I jealousy instead of putting
envidiosos y yo celos en vez de poner
that put some interesting part or
eso ponerme alguna parte interesante o
some news some bombshell that
alguna novedad algún bombazo de contarse
amador told yesterday because he doesn't tell
amador ayer porque no cuenta
absolutely anything there are live shows where he has
absolutamente nada hay directos donde ha
told more but where he has  told with
contado más pero donde ha contado con
glasses bombs is liza moza has been in the
vasos bombas es liza moza ha sido en el
slvame it is not that it is not a documentary
sálvame no es que no es un documental
that responds to Roco Carrasco that no of
que responde al rocío carrasco que no de
what
qué
in the name of Amador was going to be called
en el nombre de amador se iba a llamar
in the name of Amador and it is going to
en el nombre de amador y va a ser un
be a documentary that was sold as if it was going to respond to Carrasconte with all the covers and all the articles and the clips of the director where he sold it like that in fact they sold it as something brutal and I have all the clips okay this will tell the video on the main channel or
contará el vídeo en el canal principal o
live in conditions or I will put all
en directo en condiciones o pondré todos
the clicks that they have sold the
los clicks que han vendido la piel del
bear skin before hunting it they have already sold it
oso antes de cazarlo ya lo han vendido
as if it was going to be a roller coaster of
como que iba a hacer una montaña rusa de
emotions that there are parts that I did not know if they were going to be
emociones que hay partes que no sabía si
able to broadcast it and go ahead include it
lo iban a poder emitir y adelante
as a joke Jorge Javier
meterlo de la broma jorge javier
that Amador has told what never with
que amador ha contado lo que nunca con
such literal television in fact I think there are
tan televisión literal de hecho creo que
texts because during the edition they have
hay textos porque durante la edición han
put texts on screen that are not
puesto textos en pantalla que no vienen
relevant sometimes no but a lot of
a cuento algunas veces no pero muchos
white texts on screen
textos blancos en pantalla
with spelling mistakes and that is
con faltas de ortografía y eso es una
something that to me does seem very ugly  I know it's
cosa que a mí sí se me hace muy fea sé
an amateur report it seems like
que es un reportaje amateur parece que
a report made by a youtuber who is
un reportaje hecho por un youtuber que
doing it for the first time but don't
es la primera vez que lo hace pero no lo
sell it as what it is not you are going to do a
vendas como lo que no es vas a hacer un
report with amador and that's it not a
reportaje con amador y punto no un
documentary what has never been done on
documental lo que nunca se ha hecho en
television we are going to achieve what has not been
televisión vamos a conseguir lo que no
achieved on television literally nothing at
ha conseguido a tele literalmente nada a
most the best that was
lo más lo mejor que tuvo el directo de
last night's live was from his
anoche fue desde su propio desde su
own room and I think Kaka
propia habitación y creo que kaká nos
called us but he really wait caro
llamó pero es que realmente espera caro
didn't say anything I mean the difference between
no dijo nada o sea la diferencia entre
what chose and Ortega Cano in that
lo que elija y ortega cano en ese
right and what he said when Slvame
derecho y lo que ha dicho cuando sálvame
was chasing him is that when he
le estaba persiguiendo es que cuando
was
estaba
with the reporters from Salvamento he became
con los reporteros de salvamento se puso
foul-mouthed and aggressive and last night in the
mal hablado y agresivo y anoche en el
live broadcast he was calmer and more
directo pues fue más tranquilo y
affectionate that's the difference and you know
cariñoso esa es la diferencia y sabéis
which one sells more the one
cuál vende más
from the reporters from Slvame that will make
la de los reporteros de sálvame eso nos
more headlines for us what happened last night was
hará más titulares lo de anoche pues fue
simply a greeting to the marzipans there
simplemente un saludo a los mazapanes no
is no more salt it doesn't tell us anything related
hay más sal no nos dice nada relacionado
to any subject nothing it tells us nothing
con ningún tema nada no cuenta nada
absolutely nothing the only thing it's good for
absolutamente nada de lo único que sirve
is that we're going to have this channel
es de que vamos a tener a este canal de
YouTube
youtube
sold this family to the Mohedano
vendido a esta familia a los mohedano
media without saying anything
mediáticos sin que vaya a decir nada
bad about them for a while until they
malo de ellos durante un tiempo hasta
fight because they will fight and
que se peleen porque se pelearán y
have problems but he will
tendrán problemas pero no va a poder
never be able to criticize the bullfighter because he will
criticar nunca al torero porque le va a
pay homage to him as he did at the time
rendir pleitesía como hizo en su momento
with Antonio David at the time Don
con antonio david en su momento don
Antonio Avils paid homage he
antonio avilés rindió pleitesía le
massaged her we all love your daughter
masajeaba todos queremos mucho a tu hija
more than you he spends time enjoying them and
más que a ti las pasa a disfrutarlos a
then paying homage to him and now the
luego rendirle pleitesía y ahora el
call from Ortega is already on his channel
llamado de ortega ya está en su canal
read what he does is pay homage to him
lee lo que le hace es rendirle pleitesía
literally we are never going to see
literalmente no vamos a ver una
objectivity on this channel never never we are
objetividad en este canal nunca nunca
going to see when Amador and Ortega do
vamos a cuando amador y ortega hagan
something questionable it is not going to be on this channel
algo cuestionable no lo va en este canal
in this channel we are not going to pay homage
en este canal no lo vamos a rendir
because that channel is now going to become
porque ese canal ahora se va a convertir
the channel that cleans up the image of
en el canal que limpia la imagen de
Ortega and Amador that is what
ortega y de amador eso es lo que se va a
that channel is going to become no and has not said in
convertir ese canal no y no ha dicho en
any case really it is
ningún caso realmente ya no sirve
absolutely useless the statements are
absolutamente de nada las declaraciones
okay then
vale luego
on a technical level which is what I
a nivel técnico que es lo que menos me
care about the least it matters less  in quotes
importa menos importa entre comillas
when you go on youtube on a technical level
cuando te vas en youtube a nivel técnico
very bad very very bad why did you
muy mal pero muy muy mal para que te has
buy it it doesn't count here why did they
comprado no se cuenta acá para que te
cost you a lot of money if the
han costado muchísimo dinero si la
image is the same as the one that
imagen es la misma que la que está
the cell phone could have given they record the shots
podido dar el móvil te graban los planos
suddenly amador from here and puts
de repente amador desde aquí y les mete
the camera up their nose then he passes the
la cámara en la nariz luego le pasa a la
camera to his partner take with this the
cámara al compañero toma con esto la
camera the camera moving out of focus it
cámara la cámara moviéndose desenfocando
goes with amador's house
se va con la casa de amador
let's see it records some clear I don't know very very
vamos a ver graba unos claro no sé muy
bad very tacky very bad you can't see
muy mal muy cutre muy mal no se ve
when amador is showing the
cuando amador está enseñando las
photographs they can't be seen sir ask for
fotografías no se ven señor pide la
frame two scan them if you put them
fotograma dos las escanea si las pones
on screen to things well
tú en pantalla a las cosas bien sobre
especially if you've been editing for almost a month
todo si te has pegado casi un mes
okay those transitions that sound
vale esas transiciones ese sonido de
look what I'll tell you one thing on youtube
mira que yo te digo una cosa en youtube
there is something much more important than the
hay algo mucho más importante que la
image and sound the sound comes
imagen y el sonido el sonido es lo
first okay
primero vale
the image may be [ __ ] [ __ ] but
la imagen puede ser una [__] [__] pero
if the sound is good the video is okay but the
si el sonido bueno el vídeo vale pero el
sound was not good suddenly you could
sonido no era bueno de repente se
hear the one who was recording
escuchaba más al al que estaba grabando
with the camera more than amador because the talker
con la cámara que amador porque hablador
went over there  sant in strips that
se iba para allá sant en tiras que
started the barbosa contraption a fortune and you ca
empezó el cacharro barbosa un dineral y
n't hear okay in the sanctuary the
no se escucha vale en el santuario el
sound and the image are
sonido y la imagen
terrible you couldn't understand anything I had to put the phone to my ear to try to hear it many times the music was louder when they were in the horse-drawn carriage horrible the sound the music the sound the music and the image the image like that the image like that in the horse-drawn carriage let's
imagen así en el coche caballo vamos a
see sir buy yourself a decent
ver señor cómprate en condiciones un
strategic degree you know what I'm telling you
grado estratégico sabe lo que te digo
very bad audiovisual quality very bad very
muy malo de calidad audiovisual muy malo
bad I can't tell you anything anymore okay I
muy malo ya no puedo deciros algo vale
know it's approved okay what happened yesterday
sé que está aprobado vale lo de ayer me
seemed to me that within what he usually
pareció que dentro de lo que él suele
does it is noticeable that there has been an effort
hacer se nota que ha habido esfuerzo
okay or he has done the best he can be
vale o ha hecho lo mejor que pueda ser
but it is quite bad it is quite bad
pero está bastante mal está bastante mal
and these objectives okay when we make the
y estos objetivos vale cuando hagamos el
video on the main channel we will put
vídeo en el canal principal pondremos
all the shots and the audios so you can
todos los planos y los audios para que
see that you can't hear
veáis que no se escucha
us listen
que nos escuchen
at a content level absolutely nothing I have already
a nivel contenido absolutamente nada ya
said it does not tell anything in any
lo he dicho no cuenta nada en cualquier
salvo it has cost me much more and he has
salva me ha costado muchísimo más y ha
even told nicer anecdotes
dicho incluso anécdotas más bonitas
and then it turns out 6 years ago following the
y luego resulta hace años 6 siguiendo el
level with the technician with the
nivel con el técnico con el nivel
audiovisual level it is bought  a drone and with
audiovisual se compra un drone y con
images from other youtube channels of the
imágenes de otros canales de youtube del
lighthouse that Diego Arrabal demonstrated last night it
faro que anoche lo demostró diego
turns out that these images
arrabal resulta ser que las imágenes
that are seen of the Chipiona lighthouse
estas que se ven del faro de chipiona
surrounding the lighthouse through the air
rodeando el faro por los por los aires
the beach I don't know what he has eaten from a
la playa no sé que las ha comido de un
youtube channel and to plant the
canal de youtube y las a plantar el
documentary okay this has something wrong
documental vale esto tiene algo de malo
we also have them we have done it
nos quedan además los lo hemos hecho yo
myself I have done it on some occasions I
mismo lo he hecho en alguna ocasión no
could not say right now when it is worth
sabría decir ahora mismo cuando vale
but on some occasions well we have taken
pero en alguna ocasión pues hemos cogido
a plan or we have taken a timelapse it is
un plan o hemos cogido un timelapse es
called a timelapse which is like
que se llame timelapse que es así como
a fast camera of the landscape at some
una cámara rápida del paisaje en algún
point it is taken okay and it is done and well okay
momento se coge vale y se hace y bueno
okay but if you have bought a
vale vale pero si te has comprado un
drone if you are buying a drone with your
drone si estás compro un drone con tus
original images
imágenes originales
or in other words you are saying that you are going to
o sea que estás diciendo que le vas a
put copyright on a youtube video
poner copyright a un vídeo de youtube
so that nobody reacts it turns out that he has
para que nadie reaccione ya resulta que
leaked images well I say ramal has
ha corrido imágenes bueno digo ramal ha
said that
dicho que
Diego aralar has said that he is going to speak
diego aralar ha dicho que va a hablar
with some owners of these
con algunos propietarios de estas
images and that they are going to report them that they are
imágenes y que los van a denunciar que
going to make a claim
le van a hacer una reclamación
we will see if it is true or false and if it
veremos a ver si es verdad mentira y si
has a long way to go I think that  at
tiene mucho recorrido yo creo que como
most the journey that those
máximo el recorrido que puede tener esos
who claim money from him can have is worth employment because you have to
que le reclamen dinero vale empleo pues
pay me a percentage of what they
me tienes que pagar un porcentaje de lo
do, a documentary appears that is not
que hagan aparece documental que no es
much because as I tell you at the
mucho porque ya te digo a nivel de
number level you have to recognize that I want it, it is
número hay que reconocer que quiero
not bad it
no está mal
is a ruin on an economic level because a
es una ruina a nivel económico porque un
program that has had much more
programa que ha tenido muchísima más
investment than what they are going to earn, it is okay
inversión que lo que van a ganar vale
but it is not that they are bad numbers, bad, bad,
pero no es que sean unos números malos
bad, but they are
malos malos malos malos pero son unos
bad numbers, it is worth the one that Roco innovates, it
números malos vale el que innove rociíto
was a documentary that I made, it is worth a
era un documental que hice yo vale un
three-hour live stream that the
directo de tres horas y pico que al día
next day had 300 thousand views,
siguiente tenía 300 y pico mil visitas a
the next morning it is worth 300 thousand
la mañana siguiente vale 300 y pico mil
views and in the live stream itself it had
visitas y en el propio directo tuvo
peaks of 14,000 to 15,000 viewers and it was
picos de 14 15.000 espectadores y era un
content that I made with a lot of
contenido que hice yo con muchísima
documentation
documentación
and without any famous person in it, it is worth
y sin ningún personaje famoso en él vale
any live stream and 30,000 lines,
cualquier directo y 30.000 line
any live stream that exists,
cualquier directo de los que existan
Davis with Antonio Abilio on his channel or on
davis con antonio hábil en su canal o en
mine have had a peak of 17,18 thousand
el mío han tenido pico de 17 18 mil
viewers and we were both
espectadores y estábamos los dos
making a fool of ourselves, talking about very
haciendo el canelo hablando de sobra
good
bien
live streams that I have made with himself
directos que he hecho yo con el propio
curdle the first interview we
cuajo la primera entrevista que le
did with Diego Arrabal that had 17,000
hicimos a diego arrabal esa tuvo 17.000
peak viewers in the interview
espectadores de pico en la entrevista
we did with Antonio David that
que le hicimos antonio david eso sí que
was a historic event that was one
fue un hecho histórico
hundred thousand viewers that
eso fue cien mil espectadores que
we added up between the two of us okay
sumamos entre los dos vale
direct that direct that I am with
directos que directos que estoy yo con
Maika that for example My Car had last night what a
maika que por ejemplo my car tuvo anoche
brand well she is leaving us all
que marca bueno nos está dejando a todos
when we are all hallucinating
cuando estamos todo el mundo alucinando
because manica we have seen her in my chat
porque [__] la hemos visto en mi chat
that are no longer that she tells me she
que ya no son que ella me lo dices me
sends me messages no yes it is true
manda mensajes no que sí que es verdad
that she always needles me to collaborate
que ella siempre me aguja para colaborar
when I was on the Javi flight that
cuando estaba en el vuelo javi que esta
tonight I am going to defend you and they did not even
noche te voy a defender el y ni siquiera
know her and to follow her she is not that fast anymore
conocían y la seguir ya no es tan veloz
and the well-known ones to the engineer Avis that
y las conocidas a la ingeniera avis que
today they defended Javi flight seven
hoy te que defenden el vuelo javi siete
times and she did not want to collaborate with games
veces y no quería colaborar con juegos
in fact not in the messages that she will
de hecho ya no en los mensajes que me
send me it is that in the thousand
mandará es que en los chats de mil
direct chats you have seen her many times
directos ustedes muchas veces la habéis
criticizing downstream she curdled she
visto criticando aguas abajo se cuajó se
stuck to paying the ass for trying to
pegaba a pagar el culo por intentar
collaborate with her when she saw that it gave
colaborar con ella cuando veía que daba
a lot of audience and she  I didn't want to
mucha audiencia y ella no quería
collaborate with him because I wanted to be with him
colaborar con él porque quería con él
with mine let's say no and at the moment
con los míos digamos no y en el momento
that they are now having a better moment on the
que ahora tienen un mejor momento en el
other side
otro lado
and she lost viewers after
y ella perdió espectadores después de
positioning herself on Roco Carrasco's side she
posicionarse al lado de rocío carrasco
has returned to saying a lot of nonsense
ha vuelto a decir un montón de burradas
and defaming Roco Carrasco and now they are
y difamar a rocío carrasco y ahora están
with the other one and yesterday she was there she cut her
con el otro y ayer estaba allí cortó su
live broadcast she cancelled her live broadcast she has already
directo canceló su directo ya ha
announced saying that the
anunciado diciendo es que el documental
Avalor documentary is so interesting that we are
de avalor está tan interesante que vamos
all going there, I mean we are talking that they
todos allí o sea estamos hablando que
had a peak of 12,000 viewers
tuvieron un pico de 12.000 espectadores
with Maika and Maica's audience in the
con la audiencia de maika y maica en el
chat come on everyone light
chat venga a todo el mundo light todo el
everyone Lari
mundo lari
is when everyone is hallucinating
se está cuando todo el mundo alucinado
Vigo Mike the truth is the little leg the
vigo mike a la verdad la patita las
signs publicly the clicks are there you
enseñas públicamente están los clics lo
can see it on my twitter the kilos are
podéis ver en mi twitter están los kilos
from two months ago I was saying that you
de hace dos meses estaba diciendo que te
believed Roco Carrasco and that I was
creías a rocío carrasco y que estaba
starting to question you if everything
empezando a cuestionarte si todo lo que
Roco Carrasco said in the documentary is
dijo rocío carrasco en el documental es
the truth is that no that she is
la verdad es que no que lo está
making it up I that you said this
inventando yo que ésta lo dijiste tú en
live two or  three months okay and
directo hace dos o tres meses vale y
when you saw that she was losing followers you
cuando viste que perdía seguidores
started saying that Fidel was taking
empezaste a decir que fidel tomaba
cocaine to put her back on bikes and so on
cocaína a volverla a ponerle motos y
and now last night because of her situation
demás no y ahora anoche por su situación
with Guaje after we all
con el guaje después de que todos hemos
saw on my channel and yours and on the
visto en mi canal y en el tuyo y en el
flight that you were never going to collaborate with the one who
vuelo que nunca ibas a colaborar con el
didn't give you a good feeling that no
que no te daba buena espina que ningún
famous person would do you with the man because of the
famoso te haría con el hombre por la
people telling it there are some people who
gente contando es hay alguna gente que
follow those marzipans and you're going to have
sigue esos mazapanes y los vas a tener
the ones to worry and nothing more little you
los de preocupe y nada poco más la
put it
pongas
I
yo
sincerely can't tell you anything else
sinceramente no puedo decirles otra cosa
I congratulate her for having made an effort I
yo le felicitó por haberse esforzado
predict much success I hope
le auguro mucho éxito que ojalá se hagan
more things like that are done on YouTube
más cosas como esa en youtube
because it will keep improving I
cada vez pues se irá mejorando me
imagine and better things will be released there
imagino y se irán sacando cositas
are many
mejores hay muchos documentales que se
high quality documentaries that have been made on YouTube
han hecho en youtube de alta calidad
recently we had a documentary device
hace poco tuvimos un documental device
a documentary about willy red
un documental de willy red
and you don't need big means either
y tampoco hacen falta grandes medios
okay you have game over arrocito you
vale tenéis el game over arrocito lo
can see it I recommend it has
podéis ver yo lo recomiendo que tiene
400 thousand views
400 mil visitas
but
pero
pizza pizza or going to the family I already say
a pizza pizza o ir a la familia ya digo
at the moment that  I have light and
en el momento que tenga luz y tenga
internet, I will be with you and we will
internet estaré con ustedes y lo
analyze everything more deeply, I
analizaremos todo más profundamente
also cannot prepare any topic
tampoco puedo prepararme ningún tema
for the live because if they give me the light
para el directo porque si me dan la luz
today, there are some topics. If they give me the light on
hoy son unos temas si me dan la luz el
Monday, then the topics have suddenly
lunes pues los temas de repente han
changed completely because you know
cambiado por completo porque ya sabes
how in fact the salsero we will see each other.
como de hecho el salsero nos vemos